To evaluate how accessible any app is, you
can step through the Accessibility Testing Checklist. Some of
those steps will involve changing the accessibility settings in
the setting's app. A user will be able to
choose from these options. We have Talkback, Captions,
Magnification, increased font size, and more. I want to point
out one item in particular, Talkback service. Blind and
low vision users can turn on the Talkback service.
It allows them to navigate around the device with spoken feedback
as they interact with each UI element on the screen. There
are slightly different gestures, for example, to select or to focus
on an item. If it's the first time you turn it
on, there will be a tutorial that you can step through.
When the user navigates to these elements, Talkback service will read
aloud the context description provided. Every UI component that doesn't have
any visible text has a content
description. Using Talkback or another accessibility
tool from the checklist will let the sunshine out. Find and fix at least one
accessibility issue in the app. Then please share
what you did in the class discussion forum.